currentresults.com 2013-10-20

# Current Results Privacy Policy

Current Results Nexus respects privacy and does not collect or use personal information for any purpose. We never sell, rent or share personal information in any way with another party.

Google would also like you to know that when it displays ads on CurrentResults.com third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information while serving ads. The cookies include the DART or DoubleClick cookie used by Google to show ads based on your visits to this and other websites. 

In conjuction with AddThis, we allow third-party companies, including AddThis, to collect certain anonymous information when you visit this website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Current Results Nexus does not have access to nor control of cookies or web beacons placed by third parties.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. Turning off the browser's cookies will also prevent web beacons from tracking your activity. You can opt out of using the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You can also easily stop AddThis from collecting any information about you for online behavioral advertising by [opting out](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out). Find out more about how to [disable and enable cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).
